livenews.com.au 2008-06-23

# LIVENEWS.com.au > Privacy Policy

Macquarie Radio Network Limited owns and operates livenews.com.au.

Macquarie Radio Network respects the privacy of its users, advertisers and other people we do business with.  This Privacy Policy outlines how the Macquarie Radio Network will handle personal information about you.

**How and why we collect personal information?**

The Macquarie Radio Network needs to collect personal information in order to conduct its business.

**Website users**

Macquarie Radio Network collects personal information from listeners through our livenews.com.au website (for example, if you register as a user of livenews.com.au, or enter a competition, or provide feedback online).

Our policy is only to use personal information collected from the users of its website for the business purpose for which it was collected, and for any other purpose for which the user provides its consent.

**Advertisers**

If you or your company purchases advertising time from Macquarie Radio Network, we will collect your business contact details. We need this personal information in order to provide you or your company with our services, and to provide you with information about our services and future promotions. Unless you tell us otherwise, we will use personal information about you to market our services to you or your company.

**Will your personal information be given to anyone else?**

We will not sell, rent or trade personal information about you to or with others.

Personal information collected by us may be disclosed to third parties to whom we outsource specialised functions (such as mailing houses or printing companies), and if so, we take steps to ensure that those contractors are authorised only to use personal information in order to provide the services or to perform the functions required by us.

The only other time we would make disclosures of personal information is if we are required to do so by law, or if the disclosure is permitted under the Privacy Act.

**How is your personal information stored?**

Macquarie Radio Network takes steps to ensure that the personal information it holds is secure from unauthorised access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.  We only permit your details to be accessed by authorised personnel.

**Your right of access and correction information**

You have the right to seek access to information which we hold about you (although there are some exceptions to this). You also have the right to ask us to correct information about you which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date.

The personal information we hold about you will be information that you have provided us.

We will assume (unless you tell us otherwise) that your request relates to our current records about you. To provide you with access to "current" personal information, we would ordinarily provide you with a print-out of the relevant personal information from our databases, or with photocopies of records which are held only on paper files. We may charge you for the cost of providing this type of access, but this will depend on the scope of your request.

**Additional privacy information and how to contact us**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will make this Privacy Policy available to anyone who requests it, either at our offices or through our websites.

For further information about privacy issues, see the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/ "Link to Privacy Website")

If you feel that Macquarie Radio Network is not complying with this Privacy Policy, or if you have other privacy concerns, please contact our Chief Operating Officer (using the following contact details):

Telephone on 02 8570 0111

Facsimile on 02 8570 0222

Mail to Level 1, Building C, 33-35 Saunders St, PYRMONT, NSW, 2099
